[00:00:00]Groove Coverage ## 舞动精灵乐队
[00:02:00]7 Years And 50 Days  ## 7年50天
[00:08:59]7 years and 50 days the time is passing by  ## 7年零50天过去了
[00:15:33]nothing in this world could be  ## 这个世界上没有任何东西可以
[00:18:30]as nice as you and I  ## 你和我一样好
[00:22:09]and how could we break up like this  ## 我们怎么能像这样分手
[00:24:92]and how could we be wrong  ## 我们怎么可能是错的

